Now we have to test this. Let's go back to
我们现在来测试。 让我们再次调回
test provider once more. It'll be helpful to parameterize our tests
测试提供者。 这会帮助我们来更多的提供
a little bit more, both for location and for date.
地点和实际的测试参数。
All right, now that we've parameterized our tests, let's go back
好的， 这样我们已经把参数输入了我们的测试方法，让我们一起回去
at looking into our insert read provider. For the weather,
来观察我们的insert read provider。 对于天气的查询，
we're currently using the raw content URI to query. But we
我们目前使用的时一个原始内容的URI来进行查询。 但是我们
can also query on additional data. By cutting and pasting
可以同时通过日期查询。 通过来输入这些数值，
this text, we can try the text with different query parameters.
我们可以试着用不同的查询参数来查询结果。
We'll close the cursor because it's good
我建议大家现在可以关闭光标提示， 这是一个很好的
practice. Now for our second weather query,
练习机会哦。 现在对于我们第二个天气查询，
we're going to test the first of
我们首先来测试我们的
our new URIs: WeatherEntry.buildweatherlocation and we can use
新的URI： WeatherEntry.buildweatherlocation 同时我们要使用
our new task location parameter. Alright, let's
新的任务地点参数。 好的， 我们来试着
try running this test. And our test
运行这条测试。 测试显示通过。
passed. Alright. We're going to add one more
很棒吧。 这时我们要来加多一点
test with a slight variation on the query
测试， 这些测试是用来查询
using build weather location with start
天气地点和开始日期的查询
date, instead. So, we're going to use test
这样一来，我们将会来测试我们的地点就
location as well as test date. And now, let's run those tests. And
和我们测试日期一样了。 做完这些我们来运行下。
our tests pass. Now, sometimes it's
同样，测试通过。是时候来
useful to actually demonstrate a test failure.
写一些参数来说明我们的测试是可以失败的了。
Let's put in a date that's certainly going to fail, 20150624. We would
我们放一些能够导致测试失败的日期参数，20150624。 我们可以预料
expect this test to fail. Let's try it and indeed it fails. So
这个参数没法通过测试， 看在运行之后果然失败啦。
we're pretty sure that our tests are actually doing what we expect them to.
这样我们更能确定我们的测试是和我们的预期是吻合的